#### Contact

kendrakrogers@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/kendra-rogers-Inc-65652953 (LinkedIn)

#### Top Skills

Nursing
ICU
Patient Safety

# Kendra Rogers, LNC

MBA, BSN, RN, LNCC, CPPS, NE-BC, CCRN-K Frisco, Texas

## Summary

Experienced RN with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Legal Nurse Consulting, Patient Safety Leadership, Nursing Management, Post Anesthesia Care, Critical Care, and Nursing Education. Strong healthcare services professional with a Master of Business Administration (M.B.A.) focused in Healthcare Management from University of Texas at Tyler.

## Experience

Baylor Scott & White Medical Center at Frisco 10 years 2 months

Director, Patient Safety and Advocacy August 2016 - Present (3 years 11 months)

Asst Vice President, Patient Care Services May 2010 - August 2016 (6 years 4 months)

Asst Vice President, Patient Care bServices including Pre-Admission, Pre-Op, PACU Phase 1 and 2, inpatient post-surgical unit and Surgical Step-down unit. Responsible for 90-100 direct reports.

K. Rogers Legal Nurse Consultants Legal Nurse Consultant October 2016 - Present (3 years 9 months) Frisco, TX

Baylor Medical Center at Frisco RN Staff Nurse and Team Leader PACU 2006 - 2010 (4 years)

Baylor Regional Medical Center at Plano PACU RN 2005 - 2006 (1 year) Plano

#### **PACU RN**

Denton Regional Medical Center (subsidiary hospital of HCA) ICU RN 2005 - 2006 (1 year)

The University of Texas Southwestern Medical School RN Neurosurgery 2004 - 2005 (1 year)

Methodist Dallas Medical Center Neuro and Surgical/Trauma ICU RN 1995 - 2004 (9 years) Dallas/Fort Worth Area

RN Level 3 - Neuro, Trauma, Surgical and Transplant ICU/ER/PACU/House Supervisor. Charge Nurse and Preceptor/Educator for Nursing Internship program.

Jane Phillips Medical Center RN - Pediatric, Oncology, Urology 1993 - 1995 (2 years) Bartlesville, Ok

Pediatrics, Oncology, Urology

### Education

University of Texas at Tyler

Master of Business Administration (M.B.A.), Healthcare

Management · (2015 - 2017)

University of Georgia

Legal Nurse Consultant Certificate, Law (2016 - 2016)

The University of Texas at Arlington

Bachelor of Science (B.S.), Registered Nursing/Registered

Nurse · (2011 - 2012)

Northeastern Oklahoma A&M College

Associate's degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (1991 - 1993)